You can outnumber him. But you can't outfight him.
The Old Way is a western, drama film directed by Brett Donowho.
An old gunslinger and his daughter must face the consequences of his past, when
the son of a man he killed years ago arrives to take his revenge.
Colton Briggs, played by Nicolas Cage.
Brooke Briggs, played by Ryan Kiera Armstrong.
James McCallister, played by Noah Le Gros.
Eustice, played by Clint Howard.
Boots, played by Shiloh Fernandez.
Big Mike, played by Abraham Benrubi.
The Old Way is a 2023 American Western film directed by
Brett Donowho, from a screenplay by Carl W.
Lucas, and starring Nicolas Cage as a retired gunman on a
mission to find the outlaws who killed his wife.
The film was theatrically released by Saban Films on January 6,
2023, and received mixed reviews by critics.
The film explores themes of gunslinger, colorado,
revenge, murder, death of mother.
The tone is emotional.